A Guide to the L. T. Christian Funeral Home Records, 1912-1986
Library of Virginia
- Dunn, Lucy Evans, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Dunn, Melville Hunter, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Dunn, Patty Smith, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Dunn, Richard McIlwaine, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Dunn, Richard McIlwaine, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Dunn, Scott William, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Dunn, Susan Hill, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Dunn, Vira E., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Dunn, William Melville, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Dunn, William W., Jr., 1980 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Dunn, William Willcox, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Dunnavant, Byrd Page, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Dunsmore, Henry Hiter, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Dunsmore, Lawrence Eastman, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Dunsmore, Lawrence Eastman, Jr., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Dunston, Elizabeth Sauer, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Dunton, Nettie Rolly, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- DuPoy, Nannie L., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Dupree, John Bertis, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Durant, Grant J., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Durant, Helen Shephard, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Durfield, Frank Edward, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Durkin, Thomas, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Dutro, Laura A., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Dutro, Laura S., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Dutro, Thomas Corwin, Jr., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Duval, Alice Gregory, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Duval, John Billingsley, Jr., 1980 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Duval, Robert Cammock, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Duvall, Anne Robinson, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- DuVall, Benjamin Newell, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Dwyer, Chester P., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Dwyer, Graeme Benson, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Dyche, Homer Wilson, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Dyer, [infant], 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Dyson, Kate Imogene, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Dyson, Merton Howell, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Eads, Carrie C., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Eads, Curtis, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Eads, Harry James, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Eads, Harry Marshall, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Eagle, Henry, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Eagle, Lizzie Ketchum, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Eagles, Alice Johnson, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Earing, Minnie S., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Earl, Mary Estelle DeMaine, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Earley, Cola, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Early, Vivian Lawrence, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Earnest, Clyde Talley, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Earnest, Clyde Talley, 1958 (disinterred 1959) (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Earnest, Jessie M., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Eason, Carrie R., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Eason, Mable, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- East, Henry Sheldon, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- East, Jennie Gale, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Easterly, Catharine T., 1979 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Easterly, Katharine Friend, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Eastham, Emma Russell, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Eastman, Anna D., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Eastwood, Josephine Parkinson, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Eaton, Claud Hemon, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Eberly, Mary Rinehold, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Ecker, George E., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Eddington, Nannie Pegram, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Eddy, Sally Dunlop, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Edgar, Elizabeth Folks, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Edge, [infant], 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Edminton, Archabald D., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Edmond, Courtney, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Edmond, Emma Shipplett, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Edmond, Ida Campbell, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Edmond, Marion, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Edwards family (members unidentified), (disinterred 1972) (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Edwards, Agnes V., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Edwards, Charles M., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Edwards, Douglas B., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Edwards, Ella Stewart, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Edwards, Esther Brown, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Edwards, George Samuel, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Edwards, George Samuel, Jr., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Edwards, Ida B., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Edwards, Ida Knight, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Edwards, Lelia G., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Edwards, Lucille Wilson, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Edwards, Mary L., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Edwards, Placidia, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Edwards, William B., 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Eger, Nellie Amanda, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Eggleston, Marion R., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Eggleston, Mary E. C., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Eggleston, Mattie Wills, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Elder, Jennings R., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Elkins, Lottie Hogg, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Elkins, William Lyda, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Ellerbroeck, Jake, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Ellerson, H. Watkins, Jr., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Ellerson, Ida W., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Ellerson, Mary Patterson, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Ellerson, Roberta W., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Ellerson, Sidney Hanckel, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Ellett, Addie Cole, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Ellett, Charles Ashley, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Ellett, Ernest Vernon, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Ellett, Henry G., Jr., 1945 (disinterred 1947) (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Ellett, Henry Guerrant, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Ellett, John Spears, Jr., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Ellett, Josephine Scott, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Ellett, Mary Delaware, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Ellett, Rosalie Valentine, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Ellett, Susie McGuire, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Ellett, Tazewell, Jr., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Ellett, Thomas West, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Ellett, Thomas West, Jr., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Ellett, Virginia Randolph, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Ellington, Bayard Hamilton/Hampton, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Ellington, Bayard Hampton, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Ellington, Belle P., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Elliott, [infant] son of Warren G., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Elliott, Helen Hasteltine, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Elliott, Hugh Garnett, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Elliott, Jane Seymour, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Ellis, Joseph Thomas, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Ellis, Josiah, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Ellis, Lydia Bodeker, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Ellis, Pearl Tyler, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Ellis, Sarah Porter, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Ellyson, James Wellford, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Ellyson, Mary Josephine, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Ellyson, Nannie Page, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Ellyson, R. Selden, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Elmer, Ruth Jane, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Elmon, R. E., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Elmore, Sarah Stevens, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Elmore, Thomas Milton, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Elmore, Thornton Hunt, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Emanuel, Pauline B., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Emanuel, William Pledger, Jr., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Emison, Beatrice Taylor, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Emison, Harold S., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Emory, William Hemsley, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- English, Elizabeth Mann, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- English, Joseph Jackson, Jr., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- English, Louis Ecker, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- English, Lucy Rice, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- English, Robert Tyler, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- English, Sarah Peck, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- English, William Samuel, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Ennett, Amy T., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Enoch, [infant] son of Jack M., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Eoff, Eloise H., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Epes, Louis S., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Epes, Rebecca C., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Eppes, Magnolia Barnes, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Eppes, Margaret Gaines, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Epps, Annie McDowell, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Epps, Eva Chalkley, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Epps, Hugh Bayliss, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Epps, Kate Eaheart, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Epps, Lily Becker, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Epps, Lottie Faulconer, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Epps, Lula B., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Epps, Peter, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Epps, Peterson A., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Ern, Susan Wesley, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Ervin, Dorothy D., 1973 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Estes, James Telfair, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Etchison, Elizabeth Duncan, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Etchison, John E., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Etheridge, Julian Carr, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Etheridge, Mary, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Eubank, John Sellers, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Eubank, P. Hampton, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Euker, Carrie Thompson, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Evans, Alma Bell Wren, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Evans, Corabel Mahone, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Evans, Davis M., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Evans, Edward A., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Evans, Everett Idris, 1954 (disinterred 1955) (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Evans, Everett Idris E., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Evans, Fort Thomas, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Evans, Hazel Stembridge, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Evans, John Brook, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Evans, Lorenzo S., Jr., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Evans, Lorenzo Siebert, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Evans, Margaret, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Evans, Mary A., 1941 (disinterred) (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Evans, Maurice, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Evans, Samuel, 1941 (disinterred) (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Evans, Thomas Wellington, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Evans, William Arthur, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Evans, William Arthur, Jr., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Evans, William Edwin, Jr., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Evans, William R., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Evenson, Frederick B., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Ewart, William Cannon, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Ewart, William Fair, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Ewell, Elaine B., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Ewell, J. Davis, Jr. (see Elaine B. Ewell), 1965 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Ewig, John Frank, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Ewing, Albert Hugh, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Ewing, Charles, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Ewing, Joseph Wingfield, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Ewing, Josephine Wingfield, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Exall, Alex D., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Exall, Elizabeth Miller, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Faatz, Olleze Bishop, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Faint, Ruby Braver, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Falconer, Joseph Hamilton, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Fanear, Charles Herbert, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Fanear, Laura Parsons, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Fanney, Robert Monroe, Jr., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Fanny, Eva, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Farinholt, William Granville, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Farinholt, Wills Bacon, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Farland, Margaret Armistead, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Farland, Zebulon Skinner, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Farley, Ada Wilson, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Farley, Earnest Watson, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Farley, Josephine B., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Farley, Mary Alexander, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Farley, Mary Marshall, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Farmer, [infant] son of Claude C., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Farmer, Claude Crisp, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Farmer, Eliza Ragland, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Farmer, Frank W., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Farmer, Hettie Gilbert, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Farmer, James Henry, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Farmer, Joseph Clinton, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Farmer, Mary G., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Farnum, William George, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Farrar, Clay Holland, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Farrar, Dacre Gregory, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Farrar, Frederick Hooper, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Farrar, Grace Ladd, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Farrar, Marie Woody, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Farrar, Marion Weisiger, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Farrar, Robert Ellis Vivian, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Farrar, Robert Irvin, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Farrer, Frenanda Southall, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Farrer, Nannie I., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Farrow, Frank Lewis, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Farthing, Mabel Faucette, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Fassig, Annie Green McCoy, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Fath, Carl Woody, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Faulkner, Isabel, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Faulkner, Sara Wilson, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Fauntleroy, Elise Watkins, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Fauntleroy, Frances Fox, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Fauntleroy, Harry Wright, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Feamster, Felix Claudius, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Fee, Dorothy, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Fell, Mildred Eagle, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Fellows, Charlotte, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Felts, Dewitt Clinton, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Felts, Thomas L., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Felvey, Charles A., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Felvey, Charles A. (Jones), 1951 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Fendley, Louise Hudspeth, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Fendley, Ruth Atkisson, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Fendley, Thomas M., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Fenimore, Fred Carson, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Fenimore, Irene E., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Fennell, Ellen Jackson, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Fensom, David, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Fensom, Irene, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Fensom, John F., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Fenton, Warren L., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Fentress, Charles H., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Fentress, Sallie Taylor, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Ferguson, Allan Bernard, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Ferguson, Allan Bernard, III, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Ferguson, Hardinia Hunter, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Ferguson, Helen M., 1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Ferguson, Homer L., Jr., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Ferguson, M. B., 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Ferguson, Madeline, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Ferguson, Margaret P., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ferguson, Ruth Gordon, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Ferguson, Willie D., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Fergusson, Bertha H., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Fergusson, Edgar Bruce, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Fergusson, Raleigh Mann, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Fergusson, Russell, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Fergusson, Russell Godwin, III, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Fergusson, Virginia Jones, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Ferneyhough, Elizabeth Waller, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Ferneyhough, James Fitzhugh, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Ferneyhough, James G., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ferneyhough, John B., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Ferrell, Belle Willingham, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Ferrell, Ralph H., 1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Ferrill, Berny Duell, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Ferrin, Annie Mallory, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Fick, Mary M., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Ficklin, Dinwiddie, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Ficklin, Lucy Sale, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Fidela, Joseph, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Field, Effie Mills, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Field, Geneva Titmus, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Field, Joseph Wesley, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Field, Minnie D., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Field, Stella, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Fields, Andrew Mack, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Fields, Ben Allen, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Fields, Melissa J., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Fife, James Douglas, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Fife, Katharine Ruth Reynolds, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Fife, Robert Herndon, Jr., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Figg, Sallie Riddick, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Fill, Ira Howard, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Finch, Alice Baskerville, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Finch, Alice McKenney, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Finch, Jeanne Marie Kelly, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Finch, Margaret Sadler, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Finch, P. Gerald, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Fink, Charles G. M., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Fink, Lovely Smith, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Fink, Nancy Jane, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Finlayson, Henry Lee, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Finlayson, Herbert Lee, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Fishburne, Nevine, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Fisher, Edward C., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Fisher, Estell M., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Fisher, Harry C., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Fisher, Marcy Carmen, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Fisher, Mina D., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Fisher, William M., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Fitch, Emily Harvey, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Fitch, Harriett Garrison, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Fitz, Ernest Sherman, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Fitz, Winifred Rowe, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Fitzgerald, Alice Eliza, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Fitzgerald, DeSoto, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Fitzgerald, Elie Maury Werth, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Fitzgerald, Hendree Osborne, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Fitzgerald, Herbert B., 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Fitzgerald, Herbert Epes, Jr., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Fitzgerald, John E., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Fitzgerald, Littleton, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Fitzgerald, Littleton, Sr., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Fitzgerald, Marie Mosby Wilkinson, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Fitzgerald, Pattie Doggett, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Fitzgerald, Tazewell, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Fitzhugh, Beverly Hunt, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Fitzhugh, C. B., Jr., 1983 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Fitzhugh, Clarence Buchanan, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Fitzhugh, Lorna Allen, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Fitzhugh, Margaret W., 1978 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Fitzhugh, Mary Witherspoon, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Fitzroy, Herbert William Keith, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Fitzsimmons, Louisa deBerniere, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Flaherty, Alvin L., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Flanagan, Clifford James, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Flanagan, Edward Latane, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Flanagan, John P., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Flanagan, Kate Stuart, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Flanagan, Louis Valentine, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Flanagan, Louise Williams, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Flanagan, Samuel Codrington, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Flannagan, Elise Coke, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Flannagan, J. E. K. (see Roy K.), 1942 (disinterred 1950) (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Flannagan, John E. K., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Flannagan, Lucy C., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Flannagan, Roy K., 1942 (disinterred 1950) (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Flannagan, Roy Knight, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Flannagan, Virginia Gay, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Fleet, Alexander Hawksley, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Fleet, Anna Rutherford, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Fleet, Belle Seddon, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Fleet, Beverley, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Fleet, Elizabeth, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Fleet, Mary Heath D., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Fleet, Mollie Macgill Bridges, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Fleet, Rutherford, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Fleet, Rutherford, Jr., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Fleet, Willard Brush, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Fleisher, Charles S., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Fleming, Cannon Hobson, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Fleming, Catherine, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Fleming, Constance Keesee, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Fleming, Hampton, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Fleming, James Anderson, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Fleming, Lena Palmore, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Fleming, Mary Tomlin Anderson, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Fleming, Mattie C., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Fleming, Maysie, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Fleming, Nancy Ellett, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Fleming, Nellie George Watts, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Fleming, Peyton, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Fleming, Rives, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Fleming, Robert James, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Fleming, Sanford, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Fleming, Warner Lewis, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Flesher, Eva M. Blagg, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Fleshman, Willis Carter, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Fletcher, Carolyn M., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Fletcher, Grace Thornburg, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Fletcher, Laura Fogg, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Fletcher, Rebecca C., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Fletcher, Thomas C., 1974 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Fletcher, William A., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Flinn, Lee C. (Indie), 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Flippen, Catherine S., 1984 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Florance William Walker, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Florance, Eloise Blasingame, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Florance, James Gardner, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Florance, Juliet Walker, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Florance, Richard, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Florance, Richard Reynolds, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Florance, Willie Priddy, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Flournoy, Ann Eliza, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Flowers, Annie Cabell, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Flowers, Lemmie Hardy, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Fockler, Edwin C., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Fockler, Susan Heyser, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Fogle, Elizabeth Newton, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Foley, Estelle Mitchell, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Folkes, Grace Webster, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Folkes, Lawrence Seaton, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Folkes, Maggie M., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Folkes, Mamie Wiley, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Folkes, Minetree, Jr., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Folkes, William Wyatt, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Folline, Charles A., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Folline, Mary Gantt, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Fonville, Annie Louise, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Fonville, John Francis, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Fonville, John Francis, Jr., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Foos, Callie E. Lacy, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Forbes, Blanchard S., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Forbes, Whitmel Stallings, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ford, [infant] son of C. P., Jr., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Ford, Bertha Stites, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Ford, Harriet Timberlake, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Ford, John Alfred, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Ford, Leland Woodson, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Ford, Leslie Merle, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Ford, Lida Lee B., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Ford, Marie Thorpe, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Ford, Thomas L., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Ford, William Smith, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Fore, Bettie Atkinson, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Fore, Phillip Augustus, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Forrest, John McGee, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Forrester, Sallie Ann, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Forster, Elizabeth C., 1985 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Forster, Horace Waldo, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Forster, Louise Hally, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Forster, Margaret Leolyn, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Forsyth, Donald Murrell, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Forsyth, James, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Forsyth, Margaret W., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Forsyth, Mary Dorsey W., 1978 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Forsyth, Robert Wright, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Foster, Annie Couch, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Foster, Charles Burton, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Foster, Clinton White, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Foster, Emily Brown Hopkins, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Foster, Hugh C., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Foster, James Blackwell, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Foster, Joseph Syer, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Foster, Leslie Combs, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Foster, Marion Leech, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Foster, Samuel Miller, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Foster, William D., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Foster, William O., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Foulkrod, Sadie, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Fowler, Grace A., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Fowler, Ina Cardwell, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Fowler, John, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Fowler, John E., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Fowler, Pearl Gunn, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Fowler, Preston LeRoy, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Fowlkes, John Winston, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Fowlkes, Katherine Hurt, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Fowlkes, Lucy Meriwether, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Fowlkes, Mary Barker, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Fox, Inez, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Fox, Jennie D., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Fraley, Susie Dougherty, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Francis, Sallie Sutton, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Francis, Walter Richard, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Franke, Florence, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Franklin, Allie Lloyd, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Franklin, Edith Allen, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Fraser, Daisy Clayton, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Fraser, Jean, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Fraser, Maria, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Frasier, Caroline Martin, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Frasier, Julian G., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 8)